Guide to the Divinity School Records, circa 1920-2005 UA.19.01.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Divinity School records
circa 1920-2014
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University. Divinity School
UA.19.01.0001
156 Linear Feet
Established in 1926, the Divinity School is one of 13 seminaries founded and supported by the United Methodist Church, and attracts students from around the nation and several different countries. The Divinity School has from its beginnings been ecumenical in aspiration, teaching, and practice. This collection contains information and materials documenting the operations of the Divinity School, including the activities of its deans, faculty, students, as well as various councils, committees and organizations within and associated with the school.
Access Restrictions
For a period of twenty-five years from the origin of the material, permission in writing from the office of origin and the University Archivist is required for use. After twenty-five years, records that have been processed may be consulted with the permission of the University Archivist.
Original audiovisual media are closed to use. Access copies may be requested in advance. Some interviews may be restricted; for assistance, please consult with the University Archivist.
Provenance
The Divinity School Records were received by the University Archives as a transfer starting in 1971.
Historical Note
Established in 1926, the Divinity School is one of 13 seminaries founded and supported by the United Methodist Church, and attracts students from around the nation and several different countries. The Divinity School's distinctive vocation is to equip students for faithful leadership and critical reflection on the church's role in a dramatically changing global culture. The Divinity School has from its beginnings been ecumenical in aspiration, teaching, and practice.
Following its founding, the Divinity School (known then as the School of Religion) achieved recognition rapidly for offering above average training for all types of Christian service. While focusing clearly on the role of the minister in a local church, the school also sought to prepare missionaries, teachers, directors of religious education and social workers. Proud of its Methodist heritage and ties, the school, nevertheless, was conducted on ecumenical and not narrow denominational lines. But above all, it was launched on the strong conviction that the education offered should be based on standards of the highest level.
Chronology List
1919 Graduate School of Religion established as part of Trinity College
1926 School of Religion formally opens with 23 students and 7 faculty. Two degrees were offered, a B.D. and M.A. in Religion.
1938 School of Religion accredited
1939 First Ph.D awarded in Religion
1941 School of Religion renamed as the Duke Divinity School
1948 Petition signed by 107 Divinity School students presented to the dean requesting integration of qualified African American students.
1954 Major Renovation to the School
1961 First African American Student enrolled in the Divinity School
Collection Overview
This collection contains information and materials documenting the operations of the Divinity School, including the activities of its deans, faculty, students, as well as various councils, committees and organizations within and associated with the school. Types of documents include correspondence, reports, convocations, information about the expansion and renovation of the school, strategic plans, minutes of various council, committee, and faculty meetings, photographs, sermons, bulletins, records of the theological society and other organizations within the school, financial records, lectures, publications, subject files, statistics, deans' files, academic programs, information about field education, alumni affairs, information about faculty members, documents relating to the early history of the Divinity School when it was known as the School of Religion, and other administrative files and records.
Conditions Governing Access
In accordance with the Family Education Rights and Privacy Act of 1974 as amended, Duke University permits students to inspect their education records and limits the disclosure of personally identifiable information from education records.
Duke University -- Administration; Education, Higher -- Religious aspects; Duke University -- Students; Duke University. School of Religion; United Methodist Church (U.S.); Duke University -- Faculty; Duke University. Divinity School
- Administrative Files, circa 1920-2005; 156 Linear Feet; 109 boxes
  Scope and Contents note
  This collection contains administrative records; all administrative records are restricted for 25 years from their date of origin. Please contact research services for more information.
  Subseries in this collection have been organized by their accession numbers. An accession number is assigned to materials as they are transferred into the archives and is based on the year of transfer. Please contact the University Archives if you have questions.
  - Accession A56-698
    - Pastor's Reports to the Annual Conference, Asheville District,1941 (Box 1)
    - Pastor's Reports to the Annual Conference, Charlotte District,1941 (Box 1)
    - Pastor's Reports to the Annual Conference, Elkin District,1941 (Box 1)
    - Pastor's Reports to the Annual Conference, Gastonia District,1941 (Box 1)
    - Pastor's Reports to the Annual Conference, Greensboro District,1941 (Box 1)
    - Pastor's Reports to the Annual Conference, High Point District,1941 (Box 1)
    - Pastor's Reports to the Annual Conference, Marion District,1941 (Box 1)
    - Pastor's Reports to the Annual Conference, Salisbury District,1941 (Box 1)
    - Pastor's Reports to the Annual Conference, Statesville District,1941 (Box 1)
    - Pastor's Reports to the Annual Conference, Waynesville District,1941 (Box 1)
    - Pastor's Reports to the Annual Conference, Winston Salem District,1941 (Box 1)
    - Asheville District,1948 (Box 1)
    - Charlotte District,1948 (Box 1)
    - Durham District,1948 (Box 1)
    - Elizabeth City District,1948 (Box 1)
    - Fayetteville District,1948 (Box 1)
    - Gastonia District,1948 (Box 1)
    - Greensboro District,1948 (Box 1)
    - Marion District,1948 (Box 1)
    - New Bern District,1948 (Box 1)
    - Raleigh District,1948 (Box 1)
    - Rocky Mount District,1948 (Box 1)
    - Salisbury District,1948 (Box 1)
    - Statesville District,1948 (Box 1)
    - Thomasville District,1948 (Box 1)
    - Waynesville District,1948 (Box 1)
    - Wilmington District,1948 (Box 1)
    - Winston Salem District,1948 (Box 1)
    - Loose Papers Re: Rural America (2 Folders) (Box 1)
    - Methodist Church Statistics,1940 (Box 1)
    - Bulletins and Newsletters,1944-1947, undated (Box 1)
    - Programs and Pamphlets,1943-1947, undated (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous Minutes and Reports,1944-1947, undated (Box 1)
    - Race Relations,1941-1947, undated (Box 1)
    - The Rural Methodist,1937-1948, undated (Box 1)
    - The NC Council of Churches,1946 (Box 1)
    - Pamphlets Re: Ministerial Profession,1938-1946 (Box 1)
    - Southeastern Jurisdictional Council, The Methodist Church, Lake Junaluska, NC,1946 (Box 1)
    - Town and Country Church Newsletter,1944-1947 (Box 1)
    - New York Christian Rural Fellowship Bulletin,1945-1947 (Box 1)
    - Methodist Rural Fellowship Bulletin,1945-1947 (Box 1)
    - Loose Newsletters and Bulletins,1943-1945 (Box 1)
    - Southeastern Jurisdictional Conference Expense Fund, Report of the Treasurer,1944-1946 (Box 1)
    - Finance,1944 (Box 1)
    - Newspapers and Clippings (Box 1)
    - Forms in M.C. Census,1945 (Box 1)
    - Articles and Newsletters Re: Temperance,1941-1946 (Box 1)
    - Pamphlets Re: Rural Churches,1942-1947, undated (Box 1)
  - Accession A73-123
    - A - General Correspondence1941-1944 (Box 2)
    - Abington-Cokesbury Press, 1941-1944 (Box 2)
    - Adult Education Committee, 1944 (Box 2)
    - Akers, Susan Grey, 1941 (Box 2)
    - Alabama, University Of, 1941 (Box 2)
    - Association of American Colleges and Libraries, 1939-1942 (Box 2)
    - American Council of Learned Societies, 1939 (Box 2)
    - American School of Oriental Research, 1940-1941 (Box 2)
    - American Standard Bible Committee, 1940 (Box 2)
    - Anderson, Jack. Tallahassee, Florida, 1941-1942 (Box 2)
    - Anderson, W.K., 1941-1944 (Box 2)
    - Andrews, 1940 (Box 2)
    - Applications, 1941 (Box 2)
    - Association of American Rhodes Scholars, 1928-1942 (Box 2)
    - Association of Research Libraries, 1939-1940 (Box 2)
    - Aydelotte, Frank. Oxonian (2 Folders), 1942-1945 (Box 2)
    - B - General Correspondence, 1940-1944 (Box 2)
    - Barnes and Noble, 105 Fifth Ave., 1942 (Box 2)
    - Belgium (Publication), 1941-1942 (Box 2)
    - Bell, Frank G. Birmingham, Alabama, 1942 (Box 2)
    - Bennett, John Coleman, 1941 (Box 2)
    - Bock, Karl, 1941 (Box 2)
    - Boisen, Harold L., 1942 (Box 2)
    - Branscomb, Harvie, 1941-1944 (Box 2)
    - Brumley, Ira A., 1943-1944 (Box 2)
    - Cataloging, 1942-1943 (Box 2)
    - Christendom (Douglas Editor) Oxonian, 1943 (Box 2)
    - Coney, David, 1940-1941 (Box 2)
    - Cooke, Paul. Birmingham, Alabama, 1941 (Box 2)
    - Council of Undergraduate Teaching, undated (Box 2)
    - Crum, Mason, 1939 (Box 2)
    - Cunningham, Merrimon, 1942-1943 (Box 2)
    - Daugherty, Jim, 1940-1941 (Box 2)
    - David, Charles W., 1942 (Box 2)
    - Davidson, Chalmers G. Librarian, Davidson College, 1942 (Box 2)
    - Davidson College, 1941-1944 (Box 2)
    - Diehl, Charles E., 1944 (Box 2)
    - Donovan, H. L., 1944, undated (Box 2)
    - E – General Correspondence, 1942-1944 (Box 2)
    - Easley, J. A., 1941 (Box 2)
    - Emory University, 1942 (Box 2)
    - Ewing, Mrs. Andrew, 1941 (Box 2)
    - F – General Correspondence, 1942-1944 (Box 2)
    - Finklestein, President Louis, 1944 (Box 2)
    - Flight, John W., 1943 (Box 2)
    - Fox, Lt. F. E., 1942-1943 (Box 2)
    - Friends of the Library, 1939-1940 (Box 2)
    - Fuller, R. B., 1939 (Box 2)
    - G – General Correspondence, 1942-1944 (Box 2)
    - Garber, Paul N., 1942-1944 (Box 2)
    - Gaster, Theodor H., 1942-1943 (Box 2)
    - German Library of Information, Aug. 16, 1939 (Box 2)
    - Gilbert, A. H., 1939 (Box 2)
    - Gilbert, Katherine, 1940 (Box 2)
    - Gobbell, President (Greensboro College), 1941 (Box 2)
    - Ghodes, Clarence (English), 1938-1940 (Box 2)
    - Graduate School and Council, 1939-1943 (Box 2)
    - Graduate Sturdy in Religion, undated (Box 2)
    - Gray, Harold, 1940 (Box 2)
    - Griggs, Mrs. Lillian, 1939-1940 (Box 2)
    - Grobel, Kendrick, 1942 (Box 2)
    - H – General Correspondence, 1941-1944 (Box 2)
    - Hamilton, Mary Elizabeth Boyd, 1939 (Box 2)
    - Hamilton, W. B., 1939 (Box 2)
    - Hampden, Sydney, 1942 (Box 2)
    - Hanchet, President Virgil M. University of Iowa, 1941 (Box 2)
    - Hare, Joe, 1939 (Box 2)
    - Hargitt, George J., 1939 (Box 2)
    - Harkness, Georgia, 1941 (Box 2)
    - Harrer, G. A., 1939-1940 (Box 2)
    - Harris, Rufus C., 1944 (Box 2)
    - Harvard College, 1939-1940 (Box 2)
    - Hawkins, V. H., North Alabama Conference, 1942 (Box 2)
    - Hendrix College, 1941-1942 (Box 2)
    - Heininger, H. R. President Evangelical Theological Seminary, 1942 (Box 2)
    - Holt, Ivan Lee, 1942 (Box 2)
    - Holt, Mrs. John B., 1940-1942 (Box 2)
    - Holton, Holland, 1942-1944 (Box 2)
    - Hopper, Franklin F. New York Public Library, 1944 (Box 2)
    - Hoyt, Miss Miriam, 1940 (Box 2)
    - Huffman, Norman, 1941 (Box 2)
    - Indexing and Abstracting, 1943 (Box 2)
    - International Council of Religious Education, 1939-1940 (Box 2)
    - Iowa, University Of. Dean Packer, 1942 (Box 2)
    - Iowa, University Of., 1941 (Box 2)
    - J – General Correspondence, 1942-1944 (Box 2)
    - Japan Institute, 1939-1940 (Box 2)
    - Jewish Publication Society of America (Maurice Jacobs, Ex. Director), 1942 (Box 2)
    - Jordan, Charles E., 1941-1943 (Box 2)
    - Joyner, W. E., 1941 (Box 2)
    - K – General Correspondence, 1943-1944 (Box 2)
    - Kent, R. A., 1941 (Box 2)
    - Ketchin, Grayson Baldwin, 1940 (Box 2)
    - Kraeling, Carl H., 1941 (Box 2)
    - L – General Correspondence, 1942-1944 (Box 2)
    - Leach, James A., 1942 (Box 2)
    - Library Quarterly, Graduate Library School, University of Chicago, 1942 (Box 2)
    - M – General Correspondence, 1942-1944 (Box 2)
    - Malone, Eva, 1941 (Box 2)
    - McCorison, J. L. Jr. President, Yankton College, 1941-1942 (Box 2)
    - McGiffert, A. C., 1941 (Box 2)
    - McMillen, James A., Louisiana State University, 1941 (Box 2)
    - Mercer University, 1940-1941 (Box 2)
    - Morris, B. H., 1941 (Box 2)
    - Myatt, S. W., 1942 (Box 2)
    - Nelson, Claude, 1941 (Box 2)
    - News and Observer, 1941 (Box 2)
    - North Alabama Conference, 1941 (Box 2)
    - North Carolina College for Negroes, 1939-1940 (Box 2)
    - North Carolina Council of Churches, 1943 (Box 2)
    - North Central Association, 1942 (Box 2)
    - N, O – General Correspondence, 1942-1944 (Box 2)
    - Olivet College, 1939 (Box 2)
    - Oregon State College, 1941 (Box 2)
    - Ormond, J. M., 1942-1944 (Box 2)
    - P – General Correspondence, 1942-1944 (Box 2)
    - Peppler, C. W., 1939-1942 (Box 2)
    - Perlzweig, Dr. W. A., 1941 (Box 2)
    - Petry, Ray, 1942-1943 (Box 2)
    - Purdy, G. Flint, 1941-1944 (Box 2)
    - Query Club (Jensen and Wilson), 1942-1943 (Box 2)
    - Oxonian (4 folders) (Box 2)
    - R - General Correspondence, 1944 (Box 3)
    - Ralls, Dr. H.F., 1940 (Box 3)
    - Randolph-Macon College, J.E. Mouland, President, 1942 (Box 3)
    - Retirement, 1930-1940 (Box 3)
    - Review of Religion, Miss Marguerite Block, 1942 (Box 3)
    - Riddle, Donald, 1941-1942 (Box 3)
    - Robb, James L., 1941 (Box 3)
    - Russell, Elbbert. Dean, Duke Divinity School, 1941-1942 (Box 3)
    - Salem College, 1940 (Box 3)
    - Sawyer, Mr. O.G., 1941 (Box 3)
    - The Seven Book Hunters, 1941 (Box 3)
    - Stamm, F.W., 1944 (Box 3)
    - Stanford, Elaine, 1942 (Box 3)
    - Stechert Company, 1942 (Box 3)
    - Stern, Sidney J., 1942 (Box 3)
    - Sinespring, W.F., 1941-1943 (Box 3)
    - T - General Correspondence, 1942-1949 (Box 3)
    - Taube, Mortimer, 1939-1940 (Box 3)
    - Thomas, James A. Memorial Fund, 1941, undated (Box 3)
    - Telley, Miss Nammie M., 1941-1942 (Box 3)
    - Vassar College, Mr. Howson, Department of Religion, 1941-1942 (Box 3)
    - W - General Correspondence, 1942-1944 (Box 3)
    - Wannamaker, Dean William H., 1939-1944 (Box 3)
    - White, Carl M., 1941-1944 (Box 3)
    - White, Newman, 1939 (Box 3)
    - White, Marie, 1943, undated (Box 3)
    - Whitford, W.E., 1940 (Box 3)
    - Wolfe, R.E., 1941-1942 (Box 3)
    - Y, Z - General Correspondence, 1943-1944 (Box 3)
    - A - General Correspondence, 1943-1945 (Box 3)
    - Anderson, Troyer, 1943-1944 (Box 3)
    - April, 1945 (Box 3)
    - Allen, C.K. The Warden Rhodes House Oxford, 1943-1944 (Box 3)
    - April Issue, Oxonian (2 Folders), 1946 (Box 3)
    - Articles, 1944, 1946 (Box 3)
    - B - General Correspondence, 1943-1946 (Box 3)
    - Banta, George Publishing Co., 1944-1945 (Box 3)
    - Barnes, George E., 1942-1945 (Box 3)
    - Blackburn, Professor William, 1942-1944 (Box 3)
    - Blanshard, Brand, 1943-1945 (Box 3)
    - Brinton, Crane and Mrs. Hunter, 1942-1944 (Box 3)
    - Brook, Tucker, 1943-1944 (Box 3)
    - C - General Correspondence, 1942-1945 (Box 3)
    - Davison, Wilburt C., 1943-1945 (Box 3)
    - E - General Correspondence, 1943-1945 (Box 3)
    - Expenses, 1945-1946 (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1942-1944 (Box 3)
    - Gentry, Cyrus S., 1943-1944 (Box 3)
    - Gray, Dean C.H., 1942-1944 (Box 3)
    - H - General Correspondence, 1940-1945 (Box 3)
    - Hume, Reverend Dr. T.C., 1943-1945 (Box 3)
    - January Issue, Oxonian, 1945 (Box 3)
    - January Issue, Oxonian, 1946 (Box 3)
    - Jenkins, Mrs. H.M., 1942-1945 (Box 3)
    - K - General Correspondence, 1943-1945 (Box 3)
    - L - General Correspondence, 1943-1945 (Box 3)
    - Littell, Norman, 1944-1945 (Box 3)
    - M - General Correspondence, 1943-1945 (Box 3)
    - Material Used for October Issue, Oxonian, 1943 (Box 3)
    - Michener, Mr. D.R., 1943-1944 (Box 3)
    - N - General Correspondence, 1943-1945 (Box 3)
    - Nason, John W., 1937-1945 (Box 3)
    - New Editor - Oxonian, 1945 (Box 3)
    - O - General Correspondence, 1943-1944 (Box 3)
    - October Issue, Oxonian (2 Folders), 1944 (Box 3)
    - Oxonian Editorial Board, 1942-1944 (Box 3)
    - P - General Correspondence, 1943-1945 (Box 3)
    - Pargellis, Stanley. The Newberry Library, Chicago, 1943-1944 (Box 3)
    - Photos, Oxford, England, 1943 (Box 3)
    - R - General Correspondence, 1943 (Box 3)
    - Rhodes Scholars in Religion, 1944, undated (Box 3)
    - S - General Correspondence, 1943-1944 (Box 3)
    - Sutcliffe, W. Denham, 1943 (Box 3)
    - T - General Correspondence, 1943-1944 (Box 3)
    - Tables of Contents - Oxonian, 1933-1940 (Box 3)
    - Underwood, Eric, 1945 (Box 3)
    - Van San Tvoord, 1943 (Box 3)
    - Vowles, Guy, 1942-1944 (Box 3)
    - W - General Correspondence, 1943-1945 (Box 3)
    - Wensink, Irwin H., 1942-1943 (Box 3)
    - Winspear, Professor A.D., 1944 (Box 3)
    - Wiley, Sir Francis, 1943-1944 (Box 3)
    - A - General Correspondence (2 Folders) 1942 (Box 4)
    - B - General Correspondence (2 Folders), 1942 (Box 4)
    - C - General Correspondence (2 Folders), 1942 (Box 4)
    - D - General Correspondence, 1942 (Box 4)
    - E - General Correspondence, 1942 (Box 4)
    - F - General Correspondence, 1942 (Box 4)
    - G - General Correspondence (3 Folders), 1942 (Box 4)
    - H - General Correspondence (2 Folders), 1942 (Box 4)
    - I - General Correspondence, 1942 (Box 4)
    - J - General Correspondence, 1942 (Box 4)
    - K - General Correspondence, 1942 (Box 4)
    - L - General Correspondence, 1942 (Box 4)
    - M - General Correspondence (2 Folders), 1942 (Box 4)
    - Mc - General Correspondence, 1942 (Box 4)
    - N - General Correspondence, 1942 (Box 4)
    - O - General Correspondence, 1942 (Box 4)
    - P - General Correspondence, 1942 (Box 4)
    - R - General Correspondence, 1942 (Box 4)
    - S - General Correspondence (2 Folders), 1942 (Box 5)
    - T - General Correspondence, 1942 (Box 5)
    - U - General Correspondence, 1942 (Box 5)
    - V - General Correspondence, 1942 (Box 5)
    - W - General Correspondence (2 Folders), 1942 (Box 5)
    - X, Y, Z - General Correspondence, 1942 (Box 5)
    - Falls, R. Watson, 1942 (Box 5)
    - Letters From Alumni, 1942 (Box 5)
    - Chaplains' Letters, 1943 (Box 5)
    - General Correspondence - Macmillan Company, Ltd., 1942 (Box 5)
    - Milner, Clyde A., 1942 (Box 5)
    - Theological Education - General and Ministerial Supply, 1944 (Box 5)
    - Student Body - Robert Regan, President, 1951-1952 (Box 5)
    - Committee on MRE Degree, 1951-1952 (Box 5)
    - Registration and Schedule, 1951-1952 (Box 5)
    - Divinity School Bulletin, 1951-1952 (Box 5)
    - Ciriculum and Senior Seminar, 1951-1952 (Box 5)
    - Work Scholarship Program, 1951-1952 (Box 5)
    - Advocates, 1951-1952 (Box 5)
    - Catalogue Information, 1951-1952 (Box 5)
    - World Service and Finance, Monthly Bulletin, 1951-1952 (Box 5)
    - Gross, John O., 1951-1952 (Box 5)
    - Hargraves, Corliss P., 1951-1953 (Box 5)
    - Johnson, Henry Dr. - Committee on Ministerial Training - Emory, University, 1953 (Box 5)
    - Kentucky Conference, 1951-1952 (Box 5)
    - Louisiana Conference, 1951-1952 (Box 5)
    - Florida Conference, 1951-1952 (Box 5)
    - School for Accepted Pastors, 1951-1952 (Box 5)
    - College Sustaining Fund (B. Joseph Martin), 1951-1952 (Box 5)
    - Ormund, J.M. Fund, 1951-1952 (Box 5)
    - Episcopal Students, 1951-1952 (Box 5)
    - Western NC Conference, 1951-1952 (Box 5)
    - Alabama Conference, 1951-1952 (Box 5)
    - Baltimore Conference, 1951-1952 (Box 5)
    - Virginia Conference, 1951-1952 (Box 5)
    - Southeastern Jurisdictional Conference Correspondence Re: Appeal, 1951-1952 (Box 5)
    - Spann, J. Richard, 1951-1953 (Box 5)
    - Mississippi Conference, 1951-1952 (Box 5)
    - Jordan, C.E., 1951-1953 (Box 5)
    - Phillips, Dr. J.H. - Chaplain to the University, 1951-1953 (Box 5)
    - Bowers, H.F., 1951-1953 (Box 5)
    - Clyde, Paul N., 1951-1952 (Box 5)
    - Dozier, John M., 1951-1952 (Box 5)
    - Holston - Tennessee Conference, 1951-1952 (Box 5)
    - Archie, W.C. (Dean), 1953 (Box 5)
    - Board of Trustees, 1951-1952 (Box 5)
    - Cooper, W.G. (Secretarial Staff), 1951-1952 (Box 5)
    - President's Committee on the University Church, 1951-1952 (Box 5)
    - College Visitation, 1951-1952 (Box 5)
    - Telegrams, 1951-1952 (Box 5)
    - North Carolina Conference, 1951-1952 (Box 6)
    - Selective Service Data, 1951-1952 (Box 6)
    - South Carolina Conference, 1951-1953 (Box 6)
    - Deans - Theological Seminaries (Miscellaneous Correspondence), 1951-1952 (Box 6)
    - Whitford, W.E., 1951-1952 (Box 6)
    - Bishops of the Methodist Church (Miscellaneous Correspondence), 1951-1952 (Box 6)
    - Cannon, James, 1951-1953 (Box 6)
    - Calendar of Duke University, 1954-1955 (Box 6)
    - Chaplain Visitation, 1952-1953 (Box 6)
    - Fellowship of Professors of Missions Material, 1951-1953 (Box 6)
    - Assembly Dates and Programs and Regular Faculty Meetings, 1952-1953 (Box 6)
    - B, 1952-1953 (Box 6)
    - C, 1952-1954 (Box 6)
    - Calendars (of Duke University) (2 Folders), 1952-1954 (Box 6)
    - Cox, Mrs. Florence H. (In Charge of Crusade Students), 1952-1953 (Box 6)
    - D, 1952-1953 (Box 6)
    - Davies, Horton, 1952 (Box 6)
    - E, 1952-1953 (Box 6)
    - G, 1952-1953 (Box 6)
    - H, 1952-1953 (Box 6)
    - I, 1952-1953 (Box 6)
    - J, 1952-1953 (Box 6)
    - K, 1952-1953 (Box 6)
    - L, 1952-1953 (Box 6)
    - M, 1952-1953 (Box 6)
    - School for Accepted Supply Factors, 1952-1953 (Box 6)
    - Christian Convocation, 1952 (Box 6)
    - Convocation and Pastors' School, 1953 (Box 6)
    - Convocation, 1953 (Box 6)
    - Conference Visitation, 1952-1953 (Box 6)
    - Virginia Conference Alumni Scholarship, 1952-1953 (Box 6)
    - Virginia Conference, 1952-1953 (Box 6)
    - National Councils of Churches of Christ, 1952-1953 (Box 6)
    - Dr. E.H. Nease, 1952-1953 (Box 6)
    - Memphis Conference, 1952-1953 (Box 6)
    - Martin, Stanley H., 1952-1953 (Box 6)
    - Lugg, Thomas B., 1952-1953 (Box 6)
    - Gross, John O., 1952-1953 (Box 6)
    - North Carolina Conference, 1952-1953 (Box 6)
    - College Visitation, 1952-1953 (Box 6)
    - Commencement Exercises, 1952-1953 (Box 6)
    - Positions Available (2 Folders), 1953-1955 (Box 6)
    - Dr. Gerald McCulloh, 1953-1954 (Box 6)
    - Notices, Faculty Meetings, Etc., 1953-1954 (Box 6)
    - Assembly Periods (Speakers, Etc.), 1953-1954 (Box 6)
    - Missionary Emphasis Week (2 Folders), 1951-1952 (Box 6)
    - N, 1952-1953 (Box 6)
    - Ordination Service, 1952-1953 (Box 6)
    - R, 1952-1953 (Box 6)
    - Requisition for Payment Forms, undated (Box 6)
    - S, 1952-1953 (Box 7)
    - T, 1952-1953 (Box 7)
    - Telegrams, 1952-1953 (Box 7)
    - U, V, 1952-1953 (Box 7)
    - W, 1952-1953 (Box 7)
    - Contribution to the Divinity School, Miscellaneous Scholarships Fund, 1953 (Box 7)
    - York Chapel Correspondence, 1952-1953 (Box 7)
    - P, Q, 1952-1953 (Box 7)
    - Christian Advocates, 1952-1953 (Box 7)
    - Positions Available, 1952-1953 (Box 7)
    - Evangelistic Campaign, 1952-1953 (Box 7)
    - Board of Missions and Church Extension, 1952-1953 (Box 7)
    - Howard, W.K., 1952-1953 (Box 7)
    - The University Council, 1952-1953 (Box 7)
    - Dukes, C.A., 1952-1953 (Box 7)
    - Herring, H.J., 1952-1953 (Box 7)
    - Western NC Conference, 1952-1953 (Box 7)
    - West Virginia Conference, 1952-1953 (Box 7)